Guide to the Aaron Cometbus Punk and Underground Press Collection, ca. 1977-2013.
Cometbus, Aaron Punk and Underground Press Collection
- Series I. Punk and Underground Press Materials, 1963-2016
  - Other Locations, 1978-2015
    - Titles P-Z, 1978-2013
      - Warm Orchid, Undated; Green, Kelly; Farrell, Don; Aerol, Meg; Longacre, Barton; Savoie, Ryan; Dickinson, Paul D.; Marsenich, Milana (Box 12, Folder 126)
        Vol. 2
      - Warning, 1983-03-1985-06; Bored, Bill (Box 4, Folder 71)
        No. 3, 10-13, 15
        Anchorage, Alaska
      - Wave Motion Gun, 1991; Blythe, Randy (Box 12, Folder 127)
      - Way Cool, 1989; Albright, Lisa; Strange, Cindy (Box 4, Folder 72)
      - We Don't Go to Their Parties, 1998; Travis (Box 4, Folder 73)
      - Weapon, 1996-08-23 (Box 4, Folder 74)
      - West Virginia Surf Report, The, 1975/1982; Jeff (Box 4, Folder 75)
        No. 1, 3-4, 6
        Dunbar, West Virginia
      - White Buffalo Gazette, 1999-12-2000-04; Zenick, Jeff (Box 4, Folder 76)
        Tallahassee, Florida; Eugene, Oregon
      - Word, 1989-03-1989-05; Keyes, Tad (Box 4, Folder 77)
        Rockford, Illinois
      - Yard Wide Yarns, 1997-01-29-1998-08; Jessica (Box 4, Folder 78)
        No. 5, 6
      - Yeah, 1993; Stacy (Box 4, Folder 79)
      - Your Flesh, 1983-1984; Clark, Ron; Davis, Peter (Box 4, Folder 80)
      - YOUS, 1996; Chef Xerox (Box 4, Folder 81)
        No. 62
        Baltimore, Maryland
      - Zine Guide, 1999; Ritzel, Brent; Solheim, Jenn (Box 12, Folder 128)
        Evanston, Illinois
      - Zionoiz, 1984; Collins, Brad (Box 12, Folder 129)
        Salt Lake City, Utah
  - Underground Newspapers, 1963-1989
    - 1960s Newspapers, Underground Newspapers, and Leaflets, 1963-1966
      - National Guardian, 1963-08-15-1963-11-07 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        Vol. 15 No. 45, Vol. 16 No. 5
      - Democrat, 1963-11-07 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        Vol 3
      - The Student Voice, 1964-01-14 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        Vol. 5 No. 1
        Atlanta Georgia
      - Viet Report, 1965-17 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - News and Letters, 1965-11 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        Vol. 10 No. 8
        Great Britian
      - The Daily Collegian, 1966-01-14 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        Vol. 56 No. 54
      - In a Land Where Murder is Respectable, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC) Leaflet
    - High School Underground Newspapers, 1982-1989
      - High School Underground Newspapers, 1982-02-1989-02 (Box 17, Folder 2)
        Includes various unofficial high school periodicals
      - Contra Costa High School Zines, 1985-1986-01 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        High school underground newspapers. No. 4-10; Vol. 2 No. 3
        Contra Costa, California
  - Other Zine Materials, 1981-1994
    - Hamsterama, 1985-09; Rashkin, Elissa (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Includes zine's original page spreads for No. 10
    - Maximum Rocknroll Materials, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Includes letter to "Zinemakers" offering enclosed check as financial support
    - Nuts Article, Undated; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Includes notes about article on punk ephemera for Nuts zine, photocopies of business cards, Nuts zine
    - The Young and the Frustrated, 1985-1986-03; Ticks, Luna (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Includes letter from comic's artist Luna Ticks and examples of comic
    - Fanzines, 1985; White, Stacey (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Term Paper for Comm 85. With help from Aaron Cometbus
    - Another Room Poster, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - East Bay Tragedy, 1992; Applegren, Chris (Box 10, Folder 62)
      Donor note: These are originals for an East Bay comics anthology, edited by Chris Applegren, which was never released, circa 1992.
  - Cometbus & Related Materials, 1981-2016
    - Cometbus Issues, 1981-2016
      - (Early Cometbus) No. 5-6, 8 (2 copies), 9-13, 1981-01-1983-08; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - No. 17-19, 21-22, 1984-12-1986-03; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 11, Folder 7)
        "Pleasures of the Cometbus Harbour," "Bee That Cometbus Bracero," "Free the Cometbus 5000," "Tonight I am a Mac Magazine," "Ride the Wohl Whip Cometbus"
      - No. 23-24, 1986-1990; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 11, Folder 8)
        "Shelter from Form Farm Cometbus," "Ride the Wohl Whip Cometbus"
      - No. 27, 50-50.5, 1992-03-2006-12; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - No. 22, 26, 28, 30-38, 1985-1996; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 2)
        Includes "Ride the Wohl Whip Cometbus," "The War Years: Skrub Columns 1987-91!," "Selections From CBUS 22 and 23"
      - No. 29.5, 1993-02; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 3)
        "Clippings from the Cometbus Archives"
      - No. 40-42, 43 (2 copies), 44-49, 50.5, 53, 1997-2006-12; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 4)
        Includes "Double Duce," "St. Louis Stories," "The Dead End," "Lanky," "Back to the Land"
        Asheville, North Carolina; Pensacola, Florida; New York, New York
      - The Torah, Undated; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - No. 51-52, 2008-2009; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 11, Folder 10)
        "The Loneliness of the Electric Menorah," "The Spirit of St. Louis"
      - No. 53, 2009; Cometbus, Aaron; Polletta, Maddalena (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - No. 54-55, 2011-2013; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 11, Folder 12)
        "In China with Green Day?!!," "Pen Pals"
      - No. 55.5, 2012-09-13; Treggiari, Jo (Box 11, Folder 13)
        "Love You Like Suicide"
      - No. 55.75-56, 2014-2015; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 11, Folder 14)
        "East Bay Mostly," "A Bestiary of Booksellers"
      - No. 56.5, 2015; Jeiven, Sue (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - No. 57, 2016; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Cometbus Drafts and Proofs, 1990-2016
      - No. 31, Undated; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
      - No. 42, Undated; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - No. 43, Undated; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - No. 44, 1998-1999; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 10-11)
        "St. Louis Stories"
      - No. 46, 2000-01-22-2000-03-27; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
        "The Dead End"
      - No. 47, 2000; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 14)
        "Lanky"
      - Despite Everything, 2002; Cometbus, Aaron; Last Gasp (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Double Duce Test Copy, 2003; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - I Wish There was Something that I Could Quit Draft and Proof, 2006; Cometbus, Aaron; Last Gasp (Box 6, Folder 17)
        Includes letter from printer
      - No. 50, 2006-07-07; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Add Toner, 2008; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 19-21)
        Contains selections from Cometbus 45-48
      - Add Toner Paste-Ups, 2008; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - No. 54: In China with Green Day Final Draft, 2010-12-19; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 22)
        Released February 2011
      - No. 55: Pen Pals, 2013; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 23)
        Released February 2013
      - No. 55 3/4, 2012-05-03-2014; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Radon Draft 3, 2013-01-03; Cometbus, Aaron; Fristoe, Travis (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - No. 56: A Bestiary of Booksellers Draft 2, 2014-11-26; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - No. 56: A Bestiary of Booksellers Draft 3, 2014-12-13; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - No.57, 2016; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Add Toner Paste-Ups, 2008; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Cometbus Files, 1986-2002
      - Cometbus Assorted, 1986-2014; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 11, Folder 1)
        Includes invoices, distribution lists, flyers, clippings, correspondence
      - Cometbus Materials, 1993-2001; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 11, Folder 2)
        Includes "Direct-to-Store" spreadsheets, posters, and flyers
      - Cometbus Interviews, 1995-2000 (Box 11, Folder 3)
        Includes publications with Aaron Cometbus interviews
      - Cometbus Distributors, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
        Includes list of and correspondence from distributors
      - UK Cometbus, 1998-10; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 11, Folder 5)
        Includes handwritten notes and UK advertisements for "8 Out of 10 Days"
      - Cometbus Consignment, 1999-2002; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 11, Folder 6)
        Includes correspondence, consignment agreement and lists of locations
      - Cometbus Posters, 2002-2010; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Series II. Event Flyers and Posters, 1977-2015
  - Flyers
    Nearly every flyer in Boxes 9 and 10 have been scanned and are available through the Cornell Library Digital Collections portal.
    - Assorted
      - Archive Show Posters, 1987-1994 (Box 4, Folder 82)
      - Assorted Aaron Cometbus Flyers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 83)
      - Crackpot Flyers, 1977-1992 (Box 4, Folder 84)
      - Flyers for Non-Punk Shows, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 85)
        Folder labeled as "Not Punk but Kinda Cool/Odd"
      - Fire Relief Benefit, 2015-05-09-2015-05-17; Michaels, Jesse; Carty, Caoimhe (Box 9, Folder 16)
        1984 Printing
    - Shows: Bay Area
      - Venues A-Barb (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Barrington Hall and Benicia Youth Center (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Berkeley Square (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Venues Boo-Clu (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Club Foot (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Venues Club P - Electric (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Elite Club (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - The Farm (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Venues Fi-Ken (excluding Gilman Street Project) (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Gilman Street Project (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Keystone (Berkeley and Palo Alto) (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Venues Klu-Nov (excluding Mabuhay Gardens and New Method) (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Mabuhay Gardens (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - New Method (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Venues Ol-Om (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - On Broadway (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Venues Or-Stu (excluding Rock on Broadway, Ruthie's Inn, Sound of Music and The Stone) (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Rock on Broadway (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Ruthie's Inn (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Sound of Music (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - The Stone (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Venues Tam-You (excluding Tool and Die, Twilight Zone, and the V.I.S. Club) (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Tool and Die (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Twilight Zone (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - V.I.S. Club (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Venue Calendars (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Multiple Venue Locations (on the same flyer) (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Shows: Other Locations
      - Other California Locations (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - States A-M (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - States N-Z (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Unknown locations (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Unknown venue (Bay Area) (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - Unknown other (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Other Types of Flyers
      - Advertisements (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - Political (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Band art (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - Flyer originals (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - Band member ads (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - Gilman Street Project ads (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - Legal sized flyers (all venues) (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Cleveland Bound Death Sentence and Crimpshrine (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Pinhead Gunpowder (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Mixed oversized flyers (Box 9, Folder 17-19)
      - Green Day (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Oversized Political Posters, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
        Contains double-sided "Rock Against Reagan 1983" and "World Cannabis March on the U.N." poster.
  - Posters, 1982-1999
    - Advertisement for "Hardcore Storms America", Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
      U.K. Subs, Anti-Nowhere League. Note from donor: This caused a huge laugh. Of course, hardcore was particularly and uniquely American at that point, and certainly wasn't represented by two geezer/biker UK bands, even if the two bands happened to be pretty good.
    - Blackout Books - bookstore and info shop, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      50 Avenue B
    - Crowd surfing and moshing is not advised, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Handmade poster from a Green Day concert
    - Cub, Flake Music, Scared of Chaka, The Golden West, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Das Kriminal, War Torn Babies, Astrid Oto, Crap Factory, 1999-01-14 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Poster for a show at The HQ
      Asheville, North Carolina
    - Girlhero, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Pinhead Gunpowder "Goodbye Ellston Avenue" Poster, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Series III. Political Material, 1972-1993
  - Bush Materials, 1986-09-24 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    Includes Vice President Bush's schedule for a visit to Berkeley and his telephone list
    Berkeley, California; Phoenix, Arizona
  - Cuba for Beginners, 1972; Rius; Peoples Press (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Dan White, 1979-05-1984-01 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    Includes clippings concerning Dan White's time in prison and after
  - Article: "Du Bois and the White World Since the Civil Rights Movement", 1999-03; Olson, Joel (Box 4, Folder 88)
    Paper for the Annual Meeting of the Western Political Science Association, Seattle, Washington
    Pheonix, Arizona
  - Eldridge Cleaver, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    Includes rare newspaper columns authored by Cleaver and an introduction to the file by Aaron Cometbus.
  - Cleaver for City Council Sign and Cleaver for Congress Poster, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Poems for Potential Oppositionists, Undated; Iskra (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - Reagan Materials, 1983-1984-11; Ray, Paul; Wasteland Productions (Box 4, Folder 89)
    Includes Reagan-Bush '84 campaign stickers, "No Mondale" stickers, flyers, newspaper clipping
  - Skinheads, 1982 -1988 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    Includes articles
  - War Chest Tours, 1984; Solnit, David (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Includes letter and the article: "1984 Democratic War Chest Tours: Voting with Our Feet at the Altar of the Electoral Ritual"
  - Without Borders: Newsletter of the Anarchist Conference Festival '89, 1989; Without Borders (Box 12, Folder 131)
- Series IV. Venues, Cafes, and Community Center Materials, 1982-2006
  - ABC No Rio, 1992-2006-03 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Includes programs, zines
  - Earth Church, Undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - The Farm, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Includes letter describing notice of eviction
  - Gilman Street Project, 1986-2006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Includes notes from Aaron Cometbus, flyers, clippings, photographs, volunteer worker lists, stickers, membership cards
  - Headquarters, 1998-07-01-1999-06-30 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Includes flyers, front door key; donor note: "a collective club I was active in helping run"
  - Institute for Pragmatic Malice, The, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Long Haul Infoshop, 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    Includes flyers, calendars, and fifth anniversary zine.
  - Music Calendars, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Independent, fan-made calendars of upcoming shows and cultural events
  - Oh My, 1998-2000; Cometbus, Aaron; Crabb, Cindy (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Includes original flyers, posters, handwritten instructions for show and venue positions; donor note: "the club we ran after the demise of the Headquarters"
  - Oh My Posters, 1998-2000; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Series V. Band Files & Related Materials, 1981-2015
  Many of the event flyers in this series have been scanned and are available through the Cornell Library Digital Collections portal.
  - Aaron Cometbus Discography, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  fuck
  - Astrid Oto, 1997-2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Includes handwritten lyrics, posters, flyers, photographs, patches
  - Band Promotions, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Includes promotional photos, posters, correspondence and Aaron Cometbus note about Spinal Tap promotions
  - Band Stickers, Undated"> (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Includes Aaron Cometbus notes
  - Bay Area Peace Punk, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Includes flyers, posters, photographs, patches, Aaron Cometbus notes, and lyric /info booklet for the band A State of Mind
  - BBT Tapes, 1982-1997 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Includes Aaron Cometbus notes, tape cassette inserts
  - Best We Regret, 1994-10 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Includes drafts and notes for compilation tape liner notes about the Bay Area's punk music scene
  - Blank Fight, 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Includes flyers, patches, buttons
  - Black Flag, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    Contains flyers and an advertisement for the "Live '84" cassette.
  - Butthole Surfers, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    Includes an introduction by Aaron Cometbus, photos, letters, drawings.
  - Cleveland Bound Death Sentence, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Includes flyers, photographs, Lookout Records contract
  - Cleveland Bound Death Sentence Poster, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Colbom, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Includes original record lyric insert artwork
  - Crass, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    Contains a sketch of the origin and meaning of the original Crass logo made by Dave King, a photocopy of a letter by Joy de Vivre, and a stencilled Crass logo made by Aaron Cometbus.
  - Crass, 1982; De Vivre, Joy (Box 5, Folder 59)
    Contains letter from Joy De Vivre and Crass leaflets.
  - Crimpshrine, 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Includes posters, flyers, merchandise signs, stickers, correspondence, newspaper clippings, Lookout Records contract, photos, tour booklet
  - Crimpshrine Flyers, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Transparencies, and show flyers
  - Crimpshrine: Letters to Crimpshrine, 1988-1997 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Crimpshrine posters, 1984-1995 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Crimpshrine, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    Includes newspaper clippings, photos, lyric booklets, paste-ups for lyric sheets and tape inserts.
  - Crimpshrine Tour Book, 1988-07-1998-09 (Box 17)
  - Crook Invasion, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Includes demo tape cover and lyric sheet
  - Dangerous Rhythm, Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Includes Aaron Cometbus note and advertisement
  - Devo, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    Contains news clippings, postcards, and photographs.
  - Fake Show Flyers, Undated; Bucher, Richie (Box 10, Folder 68)
    Includes introduction by Aaron Cometbus.
  - Fang, Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Flipper, 1982-1989 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    Includes photocopies of newspaper clippings, photograph, dolphin image, poster, tour flyer.
  - Fuck Shit Piss, 1985-07-14-1987-05-02 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Show flyers
    Nevada
  - Green Day, 1989-2017 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Includes stickers, photographs, flyers, tour schedule
  - Two handmade posters from Green Day concert, 1990-06-1990-06 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Selling L.P.s, T-shirts, socks, and Cometbus fanzines. Posters written on the back of a flyer for Monsula and Sawhorse Summer Tour 1990.
  - Harbinger, Undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
    Includes flyers and photographs.
  - Harbinger Poster, Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Hüsker Dü, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Includes interview and press packet from first national tour
  - Jawbreaker, 1996-05-2002-06; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Includes original handwritten lettering for LP.
  - Lest We Forget reissue, 2018 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    1991 issued, 2018 rereleased.
  - Lookout Records, 1987-12-1998-10 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Includes flyers, posters, catalogs
  - Lyric Sheets and Songbooks, 1982-2000 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Includes sheets and booklets from Bikini Kill, Operation Ivy, Crucifix, Atrocity, Trial, Econochrist, Filth, Treason, The Gr'ups, The Quails, and Ten Tall Men, No. 47
    Donor note: These aren't record inserts, they are from a time when most bands handed out lyric sheets at shows.
  - Mr. T Experience, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    Includes newsletters, posters, flyers, photographs, clippings and a copy of the MTX fan club zine.
  - Mundt, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    Contains photocopied cassette insert and artwork.
  - Offspring Check, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    Includes a donor note by Aaron Cometbus and photocopies of a check written out to him from the band.
  - Operation Ivy, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    Includes flyers, newsletters, and original artwork by Jesse Michaels
  - Pinhead Gunpowder, 1990-2015 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    Includes handwritten lyrics, reviews, individual disbursement reports, posters, flyers, clippings, correspondence
  - Pinhead Gunpowder Posters, 2003-10-21-2008-02-04 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Pinhead Gunpowder Printer Proofs, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Record Inserts, >Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
    Includes Peace Energy Action Cooperation Evolution (PEACE)
  - Redmond Shooting Stars, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    Includes flyers, photos, letters, and artwork paste-ups.
  - Retard Beaters, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Includes flyers, labels, lyric sheet
  - Rick Rubin/ Hose, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    Contains introduction to the file by Aaron Cometbus and a handwritten note by Rick Rubin.
  - Rummage Sale, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    Contains original artwork and lyric sheet paste-ups.
  - S.A.G., 1982 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Scooby Don't, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    Containers flyers and a Dillinger Four set list.
  - Screeching Weasel, 1987-1994 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    Includes 1988 issue of Empire Monthly, newsletters, posters, a letter from Ben Weasel, and an introduction to the file by Aaron Cometbus.
  - Set lists, 1977-1985 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Atrocity set list, 1984 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Poster sized set list from a show at Club Foot in 1984
  - Shotwell Coho, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    Contains flyers and a lyric sheet paste-up.
  - Sweet Baby, 1989-1996 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    Contains photographs, flyers, set lists, news clippings, and posters.
  - Sweet Baby Poster, Undated (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Tours and Tour Phone Numbers, 1988-1991 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    Contains contacts from several different band tours, including Crimpshrine, Sweet Baby Jesus, and Green Day
  - T. Zatana, Undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - X, Undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - X Poster, 1981 (Mapcase-folder 1)
- Series VI. Ephemera, 1979-2018
  - Photographs
    - Mixed Photographs, Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Murray Bowles Photographs, Undated; Bowles, Murray (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Assorted Ephemera, 1982-2018
    - Assorted Publications, 1984-2010 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      Includes zines, programs, record catalogs, pamphlets
    - Barrington Hall, 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 67)
      Contains flyers and news clippings.
    - Berkeley Punk Assorted, 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      Includes clippings, stickers, photographs, flyers, Aaron Cometbus notes
    - Birthday Cards, 1990-1999 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      Includes cards from Aaron Cometbus to others
    - Bobby Madness, 1988; Madness, Bobby (Box 10, Folder 61)
      Contains reproductions and original illustrations by Ithaca-born artist Bobby Madness, as well as an introduction by Aaron Cometbus.
    - Business Cards, Undated"> (Box 5, Folder 42)
      Includes business cards, Nuts zine, and note from Aaron Cometbus
    - Ephemera, 1985-1996; MU-1880-1882 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      Includes ticket stubs, clippings, flyers, stickers, photographs and an invitation to Jello Biafra and Therese Soder's wedding. Also includes a Public Humiliation lighter (MU-1880), Isocracy matchbook (MU-1881), and Captain Crunch guitar pick (MU-1882).
    - Fleabites Calendars, 2004-2018 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Fleabite Calendars, 2017 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Hard Times Café, 2000-02-2001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Includes articles, correspondence, inspection report, notice of nuisance, notice of complaint notice of hearing, matchbooks
    - Hedgediving, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Includes a letter describing the mid-1980's Berkeley practice of hedgediving
    - Mainstream Portrayals of Punk, 1985-1998 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Patches, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Includes 3 cloth patches
    - People's Park, 1987-1997 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      Contains flyers, photographs, and news clippings.